Do you know where our child is?
She might be in Cebu
with our future in-laws.
Mario and Tess
are not returning our calls.
We should reach out to them aggressively.
Let's give them a grand emmisary.
You're the one
who had a lot of doubts in Mikoy.
But you still believe
that we should find him and save him.
I think there's only one place
where they know where Mikoy is.
Cebu.
I was the last person La Fornarina
spoke to before she disappeared.
Say hello to Marga Espinosa
and Dasho Malabanan.
Why? Do you want to be like that?
I want to, but it seems impossible.
Our relationship survived
in the midst of pretending.
Whatever happens,
there's always tomorrow that awaits us.
In-laws! How have you been?
What brings you here so suddenly?
Sorry, we weren't able
to let you know sooner.
Mario, Tess.
We're in-laws, aren't we?
It's been a while since we experienced
the Pinagpala hospitality.
We've missed you so much.
Just the two of us.
That can only mean two things.
First, Viktor is here to fish
for information from the Pinagpalas,
or Viktor is bringing them information.
Either way, we don't have access
to that information.
Whether it's from Mario or from Viktor.
I have an idea.
I know what we're going to do
so we can get the information ourselves
through their family.
How have you been, in-law?
Leave us alone for a moment.
‪Well.
I'm okay. Life goes on.
Even with things happening
that I can't control.
As for me,
I've been having trouble sleeping.
Donabel says
my skin is getting dry.
But yours
still look fresh. How?
You know, in-law.
I already know the truth.
So we don't need to talk about the thing
we're not supposed to talk about.
I understand that we shouldn't
talk about the things
that shouldn't be discussed.
Well, in-law, no matter what happens,
you still need to take care of yourself.
I mean,
how many steps is it?
Viktor, stop beating around the bush.
What is it really?
But in-law, I'm really shocked.
How were you able to get into that?
The thing that we're not
allowed to talk about.
nor deny what you're calling
the thing that shouldn't be discussed.
I don't know what you've heard about me.
Maybe some of those things are true.
But for sure, many of them
are just exaggerations.
in-law.
is I'm not the enemy of my own child.
And I'm not the enemy of the person
she loves the most.
I'm an ally here.
An ally?
You know, whether it's true or not,
I'm not here to judge you, in-law.
But if the opportunity comes,
maybe you can finally
turn your back on that thing
we're not allowed to talk about.
If only life were that simple,
as if it were a hot potato
you could just spit out.
Right?
It's not that simple, in-law.
So let's stop talking about
what shouldn't be discussed.
And they never stop
trying to bring me down.
You know, here's my point.
Even if I don't agree
with the life you've chosen,
that thing we're not supposed to discuss,
as a mother,
we need to talk about
what we're not supposed to talk about.
Because you know,
Mikoy truly loves Chiara.
And my only obligation as a parent
is to understand him, right?
Because he knew the complications
of the life he entered.
The one we're not allowed to discuss.
Well.
You know, I'm sorry, in-law,
but as of today,
I still haven't spoken to Mikoy.
That's quite strange.
Very strange.
Well,
we can sing
all the Eraserhead songs you want,
but that's the truth.
I still haven't spoken to Mikoy.
I don't even know
where Mikoy is. Or…
I don't know where Mikoy and Chiara is.
We need to talk about the things
that have not been discussed.
What are we not supposed to talk about?
Sweetheart. Are you okay?
I can't relax.
Why? Is there a problem?
Oh.
You know…
I've noticed that we must be
really special to you.
Imagine
that you've got another
special delivery of your…
torta.
Of course, sir. This is a special
Pinagpala torta delivery.
Cut, sir. Cut it out, sir. Yes.
You, sir!
I know what you're doing.
It's already 2026!
I'm aware of those tricks.
Just because you know that
I find you super duper handsome,
you're taking advantage of it, huh?
Oh, you. As if.
You think that with all your charm,
I'd just suddenly jump ship
and join your side,
just like that?
Oh, no!
Because I, Bechay of Cebu,
do solemnly swear my loyalty
to the Pinagpala family
forever and ever, amen!
You know,
you're such a beautiful brunette, so much,
but you're also very smart.
I'm just curious.
Why are you so loyal to the Pinagpalas?
I'm sure in a place like this,
there are families that are
more influential, wealthier,
and have businesses where you could work.
What is it about that family
that makes you so loyal to them?
It's simple.
They're good people.
You don't need a long essay
or some complicated reason
to stand on the side
of what's right. Isn't it?
Did you know?
People here absolutely love them.
They never needed a government position
to help other people.
In their own simple way,
the good things they've done
have left a mark on this community.
As for me,
before my glow-up,
and before I became known as Bechay,
I started out with nowhere to stay.
Because I was an orphan.
Not one of my relatives took me in.
Only the Pinagpalas did.
They didn't just open their home to me.
They also opened their kindest hearts.
Especially Mikoy.
Oh my, he's practically
like a brother to me.
Oh, no.
He's crying! He's crying!
See? It worked.
- My story was supposed to be
- No!
- primetime-worthy.
- What are you talking about?
It's just my rhinitis acting up.
- Here.
- Wait.
This works for my allergic rhinitis.
Liniment.
You can have it. My gift to you.
Do we really have to leave right away?
Are you sure? Why?
Did someone see you?
I had a strange feeling earlier.
I thought someone was following me.
Are you sure?
Well, if you're sure,
then it's not a problem.
We can leave.
Something tells me we're not safe here.
There's nothing wrong with overreacting.
Chiara, this is your world.
You know more about this than I do, okay?
So we will always follow your instincts.
You know?
We've only just started here.
Do you know how hard it is to run
and start over somewhere else?
But if that's really how you feel,
then okay.
Let's just leave.
Actually, I haven't really seen
anything yet that could
put our lives at risk here.
You know,
that's why I always admire you,
because I know how difficult and chaotic
the world you came from is.
From now on,
stop thinking that you need to protect me.
Okay?
I should.
From now on,
I'll be the one protecting you.
I will do everything I can to make sure
nothing bad happens to you.
Okay?
There's not even a distributor.
It's not even available on seller markets.
Are you sure?
Wait. Who gave that to you?
The people from the Pinagpala family.
Are you going to tell Agent Alex?
Wait, then…
She'll be able to find Mikoy.
What about your love team?
Dara, do you really think that's
what I'm worried about right now?
Then I guess not.
Isn't it ironic? If I'm right,
deep down, you really don't want
Mikoy to be found.
But in the end,
you'll be the one who find him.
Bye!
What an idiot.
That is a futile exercise.
You won't get anything from them.
Everyone here is loyal to the Pinagpalas.
Why are you so quiet?
Don't tell me you're thinking about
fried chicken again.
No.
I have something else in mind,
and I'm sure you'll be interested in it.
Jungkook?
Jungkook? No!
It's Mikoy!
Hong Kong?
Wait, what makes you say that?
And how did you come up with that theory?
Yes, Mikoy is in Hong Kong.
A logical conclusion
based on existing information
and on the observations we have.
You know, I don't need
a science lecture refresher.
I'm not lecturing you, Bok, okay?
Where is it now?
Here's the thing.
Look, this.
This liniment
is exclusively available in Hong Kong.
Even from online resellers
here in the Philippines,
you can't buy this.
If you ever happen to find one,
it's fake, okay?
And it's true.
What you said is true. Bechay said
that when it comes to family,
the Pinagpalas are solid.
They always stick together.
But imagine,
this is exclusive to Hong Kong.
How would people in Cebu
get their hands on this liniment
if it's exclusively available
in pharmacies in Hong Kong?
Sir, we now have enough
solid leads on Chiara and Mikoy.
What?
Alex went to Hong Kong?
For her, there are already
verified leads in the area.
Enough for her to mobilize too.
It's still under minimal circulation, sir.
Me, Dara, logistics.
so we can avoid any misencounters.
Sweetheart. Sweetheart, wake up!
We have to go!
- Huh? Why? What happened?
- Get dressed. Hurry!
Wait, what's going on?
We don't have time. We have to go now!
They've found us.
And what exactly is CHENES?
Sir, they only use that if there is
coordinated law enforcement in Hong Kong.
But I have a strong feeling that this
Code Red is for Mikoy and Chiara.
Hey, we have a visitor! Hello!
How's your Dad? Does he know you're here?
Actually, I'm applying to your bakery.
Huh?
Is Mikoy here?
Is he with Chiara?
You know that I'm not allowed
to help them.
Norberto, we're talking about my son here!
After what I did for you,
this is how you pay me back?
I have something in mind
for them to escape in Hong Kong.
Are you ready?
Okay.